Guide to the Houston Area Asian Archives oral history interviews and related materials, 2003-2021 MS 573
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
Houston Asian American Archives oral history interviews and related materials
2003-2021
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas https://library.rice.edu/woodson
Rice University Chao Center for Asian Studies
MS 573
8 Linear Feet (14 boxes and digital objects)
This is a collection of oral history interviews conducted by the Chao Center for Asian Studies, featuring audio recordings and transcripts of interviews with Asian Americans native to Houston.
Biographical / Historical
The Chao Center for Asian Studies is a research institute attached to an undergraduate major at Rice University. The Center supports a model of Asian Studies that looks carefully and critically at the complex ways people in 'Asia' have been involved with one another and with the rest of the world, not only today, but also in the past. Toward these ends, they work closely with peer organizations in inter-Asia, indeed, in some cases with those whom they study, and in every case collaborating with scholars who pursue similar questions as they do.
The Chao Center for Asian Studies builds on the core initiatives outlined in Rice University President David Leebron's "Vision for the Second Century." These are: (1) visibly and substantially increasing our commitment to our research mission and raising our research and scholarship profile; (2) aggressively fostering collaborative relationships with other institutions to leverage our resources; (3) becoming an international university, with a more significant orientation toward Asia and Latin America than now characterizes our commitments.
(This information was excerpted from the Chao Center for Asian Studies website http://chaocenter.rice.edu/about-the-center.aspx on December 1, 2010.)
Scope and Contents
This is a collection of oral history interviews conducted by the Chao Center for Asian Studies at Rice University. This collection includes audio recordings and transcripts of interviews with the following Asian Americans native to Houston: Edward Chen, Esther Quan, Gene L. Lee, Lewis Yee, Jane Gee, George Gee, Viola Chan, Wea Lee, Eugenie Chen, and Hannah Chow. The interviewees include a former rocket scientist and high school chemistry teacher, a founding member of the Chinese American Citizens Alliance, a World War II veteran, and the publisher of a Chinese newspaper in Texas and owner of the first Chinese printing company in Houston.
There are currently 147 English language audio interviews in the collection, mostly dating from 2010-2015, with expectation that more new interviews will be added annually.
Conditions Governing Access
This material is open for research.
Conditions Governing Access
Stored onsite at the Woodson Research Center.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
This material was transferred from the Chao Center for Asian Studies beginning in 2010, through the present.
Related Materials
See also:
Edward C.M. Chen Family Collection, 1920-2010, MS 561. Finding aid: http://library.rice.edu/collections/WRC/finding-aids/manuscripts/0561
Gene & Hedy Lee Chinese language newspapers & photographs, 1962-2010, MS 556. Finding aid: http://library.rice.edu/collections/WRC/finding-aids/manuscripts/0556/
Accruals
Additions to this collection may be expected over time.
Separated Materials
Books cataloged separately:
Philippine Nurses Association of Metropolitan Houston: 30th anniversary & induction of 2010-12 Executive Board. Houston, Tex.: The Association, 2010.
442 [videorecording]: live with honor, die with dignity / 442 Film Partners present a UTB Pictures and Film Voice production; written and directed by Junichi Suzuki. Hollywood, CA: United Television Broadcasting Systems, 2010. "Testimonies of former veterans including Senator Daniel K. Inouye and interviews with actor George Takei and prominent community leaders tell the largely unknown stories of unprecedented military bravery and valot of the veterans." Fondren Library call # D769.31 442nd .A14 2010
The Gees in Houston, Texas. Published by Gee Family Association, 1998.
Index Terms
Document Types
transcripts; audiotapes; digital audio formats
Places
Asian Americans
- Series I: Oral history interview by last name, A-M
  - Selina Ahmed oral history, 172624 (Box 1)
    Scope and Contents
    Includes transcript, consent form, research notes, photographs, and newsclippings.
  - Ameen, Nusrat, 2018-05-29 (Box 1)
  - Susan Annoura oral history interview, 212185 (Box 1)
    Includes transcript, consent form, and photographs.
  - Keiji Asakura oral history, 2014-04-05; 181488 (Box 1)
  - Prabha Bala, 2018 (Box 1)
  - Sundaresan "Sesh" Bala oral history, 172631 (Box 1)
    Includes transcript, consent form, research notes, photographs, and event program.
  - Zarine Balsara oral history (Box 1)
    Includes transcript, consent form, and research notes.
  - Banon, Kathy, 123464 (Box 1)
    Includes transcript and audio.
  - Gloria Baterina oral history interview, 212186 (Box 1)
  - Sonal Bhuchar oral history, 172606 (Box 1)
    Includes transcript, consent form, research notes, and photographs.
  - Feroze Pejhotan Bhandara oral history (Box 1)
  - Boyce, Mrs. Zarine H. and Dr. Meherwan P. (no consent to post online), 123485 (Box 1)
    Includes transcript, consent form, survey, audio, and photographs.
  - Brenneman, Dolly (Nguyen-Son Le-Hang), 2018-03-20 (Box 1)
  - Victoria Ai Linh Bryant, 160609 (Box 1)
    Includes transcript, consent form, audio, interview questions, questionnaire, and photographs.
  - Huyen Bui oral history (Box 1)
    Includes transcript,research notes, and questionnaire.
  - Ramon L. Burdeos, Jr., 160610 (Box 1)
    Includes transcription and consent form.
  - Cabio, Meryl Lou, 2020-03-11 (Box 2)
  - Calvert, Rogene Gee, 159580 (Box 2)
    Includes transcript, audio, survey, and resume.
  - Chan, Lawrence (Box 2)
  - Viola Chan, 2010, 114925 (Box 2)
    Includes transcript, consent form, audio, and photographs.
  - Chang, Jackson, 123465 (Box 2)
    Includes transcript, questionnaire, consent form, and audio.
  - Chang, Peter, 2018-06-20 (Box 2)
  - Chang, Teh Cheong, 2018-06-08 (Box 2)
    FOlder also contains a packet of clippings and images regarding Chang's architectural accomplishments, tennis champioships, as well as biographical note. An additional volume is "Harry Weese and Associates, Architects Engineers Planners," published circa 1978.
  - Chang, Theresa, 132936 (Box 2)
    Includes transcript, consent form, audio, and news clippings.
  - Stephen Chao oral history, 2014-03-30; 181493 (Box 2)
  - Chen, Alice, 159588 (Box 2)
    Includes transcript, consent form, audio, newsclippings, and photographs.
  - Annie Chen oral history, 168320 (Box 2)
    Includes transcript, consent form, research notes, and audio.
  - Edward C. M. Chen, June 4, 2010, 114906 (Box 2)
    Includes transcript and questionnaire.
  - Eugenie Chen, July 12, 2010, 114936 (Box 2)
    Includes consent form, and transcript.
  - Chen, Shane, 2017-06-23 (Box 2)
  - Chen, Wei-Gwo, 123469 (Box 2)
    Includes consent form and transcript.
  - Faye Chin oral history, 172559 (Box 2)
    Includes consent form, transcript, and photographs.
  - Chin, Faye, 2018-05-12 (Box 2)
  - Chiou, George, 2019-04-05 (Box 2)
  - Chou, Lynn Ling-Ying, 2018-06-25 (Box 2)
  - Hannah Chow, July 14, 2010, 114939 (Box 2)
    Includes consent form, transcript, and Texas State Senate Proclamation No. 1593 honoring Judge Hannah Chow for her service to Houston and Harris County (undated facsimile of document signed by Sen. Rodney Ellis).
  - Chu, Bao-Long, 2018-04-20 (Box 2)
  - Chu, May, 2019-01-19 (Box 2)
    Not approved for online publication.
  - Gene Chung oral history, Fall 2017, 2017-09-13 (Box 2)
  - Chung, Tiffany (not available online), 2020-08-20-2020-09-11 (Box 2)
  - Donna Fujimoto Cole, 160611 (Box 2)
    Includes consent form, questionnaire, transcript, photographs.
  - Sarosh Collector, 2014 (Box 2)
  - Thao Costis oral history interview, 260484 (Box 2)
    Includes consent form and transcript, but no photographs.
  - Cuenca, Isabel, 2019-04-20 (Box 2)
  - Dang, Thieu, 2018-10-26 (Box 2)
  - Thong Dang oral history, 168325 (Box 3)
  - Tuong Vy Dang oral history, 168329 (Box 3)
  - Homi Davier, 2014 (Box 3)
  - Daya Client (Anonymous), 2012-06-18 (Box 3)
  - der Bing, Eleanor, 2017-06-15 (Box 3)
  - Thrity Desai, 2014 (Box 3)
  - Di, Francine, 2019-07-24 (Box 2)
    Also includes event programs and newsclippings featuring Di.
  - Dinh, Duc Cong, 2011, 123470 (Box 3)
  - Tammy Do oral history, 169582 (Box 3)
  - Doan, Trung H., 2012, 159592 (Box 3)
    Includes consent form, transcript, photographs, and questionnaire.
  - Kaemerz Dotiwala, 2014 (Box 3)
  - Rustom Engineer, 2014 (Box 3)
    Includes consent form, transcript, personal documents and photographs.
  - Fong, Cecil, 2019-06-08 (Box 3)
  - Fujimoto, George, 159597 (Box 3)
    Includes consent form, but no transcript. Also includes documents such as Vibrant Vitality of Houston business card and brochure (print copy); and News article "Patients get vibe of device", The Hutchison News, March 5, 2006 (print copy).
  - Fujimoto, Yoshio "Willie", 2018-07-31 (Box 3)
  - Funk, Kathleen Santos, 2012, 159602 (Box 3)
  - Beck Gee, 2017 (wrc08292) (Box 3)
  - George Gee, June 17, 2010, 114923 (Box 3)
    Includes consent form and transcript, as well as Outstanding achievement award newsclipping, 2007, by OCA Houston.
  - Gee, Gordon, 2012-09-06 (Box 3)
  - Harry Gee interview, including 2 photocopies of images, of Chinese Village drive-in restaurant and Chinese Baptist Church members (Houston) taken in early 1940s, 2012; 160612 (Box 3)
    Includes consent form, transcript, photograph, questionnaire, and 2013 Christmas letter.
  - Henry S. Gee, 2012 (Box 3)
  - Gee, Raymond oral history, Fall 2012 (Box 3)
  - Gee, Shelton, and Chong, Judy Gee, Fall 2012 (Box 3)
    Includes transcript and consent form.
  - Jane Gee, June 16, 2010, 114918 (Box 4)
  - Kalyani Giri, 2013, 172618 (Box 4)
    Includes consent form, transcipt, photograph.
  - Gondo, Glen Yoshiaki, 2011, 132872 (Box 4)
    Includes consent form, transcript, resume, photograph.
  - Gor, Beverly, 132877 (Box 4)
    Includes consent form, transcript, photograph, Quan family tree.
    - Beverly Gor awards and recognitions (Box 13)
      - Outstanding Preceptor Award (2013): Plaque from the Houston Academy of Nutrition & Dietetics presented to Dr. Beverly Gor
      - Certificate of Appreciation: Presented from the USDA Center for Nutrition Policy and Promotion, recognizing Dr. Beverly Gor's work with CAN DO Houston
      - Certificate of Appreciation (04/29/13): Presented during Health Awareness Month recognizing Dr. Beverly Gor's "invaluable community service promoting health equity and reducing health disparities"
      - Outstanding Preceptor Award Veteran (2013): Award presented from the Texas Academy of Nutrition and Dietetics to Dr. Beverly Gor
      - TDA Media Award (2007): Plaque presented from the Houston Area Dietetic Association
      - Nursing Excellence: Problem Solving, Populations, and Performance (July 27, 2014): Plaque recognizing Dr. Beverly Gor for Presenting "Health and Cancer needs of Asian Pacific Islanders: Stories from the 'Model Minority"
      - Appreciation Plaque (March, 2004): Plaque from the Houston Department of Health and Human Services "in appreciation of [Dr. Gor's] time and support of [the] WIC Nutrition Education Program"
      - Origami Frame (June, 2007): Presented from the Asian American Health Coalition/HOPE Clinic "in appreciation for [Dr. Gor's] selfless dedication and servant leadership in establishing HOPE Clinic"
      - National Forensic League Certification (11/18/70): Award certifying that Dr. Gor was elected as a member of the National Forensic Leage at Houston-Milby
      - Certificate of Appreciation (07/27/02): Presented from the Stand Against Violence Everyone Alief organization for Dr. Gor's contributions to the Alief Health and Civic Resources Fair.
      - Certificate of Appreciation (07/19/00): Presented to Dr. Gor from the Texas Health Steps Outreach Workgroup for her guest presentation "Reaching Out to the Outreach Worker"
      - Recognition Award (2004): Presented from the Texas Cancer Council in recognition for Dr. Gor's service to the Texas Cancer Plan Update Project
      - Seminar Speaker Plaque (July 4, 2009): Presented from the Federation of Bangladeshi Associations in North America to Dr. Gor for her work as the Seminar Speaker at the FOBANA 2009 Convention
      - University of Texas Graduation Appreciation Award (2004): Presented from Rachel Gor to her parents for "...helping [her] to attain this most important milestone of [her] life"
      - Distinguished Dietitian Award (2004): Presented by Jill Campbell of the Houston Area Dietetic Association to Dr. Beverly Gor
      - Framed Newspaper Article (01/25/02): (Text in Chinese)
      - Wooden Frame with Script: (Text in Chinese)
    - Beverly Gor family photos, 1980-2010
      General
      Contains photos from Beverly Gor's mother and father's photo albums: "Lung Kong Lodge, San Francisco" and "To Mr & Mrs. Gordon Quan, From Uncle Paul & Aunt Mae, 1981."
  - Goradia, Marie, 2019-02-23 (Box 4)
  - Goradia, Vijay, 2019-02-16 (Box 4)
  - Goswami, Meghna (not available online) (Box 4)
    Conditions Governing Access
    Restricted from any research for 20 years after donation. Transcript preserved in administrative control folder.
  - Gulati, Jaimeet (no audio), 174333 (Box 4)
    Includes transcript and research notes, but no audio.
  - Zenobia Guzder, 2014 (Box 4)
    Includes consent form, transcript and photographs.
  - Gyawali, Ritu (reading room access only), 2018-09-14 (Box 4)
  - Ha, Christine Huyen Tran, 2019-02-09 (Box 4)
  - Haj-Ismail, Imad Adel, 123475 (Box 4)
    Includes consent form, transcript and questionnaire.
  - Hirasaki, George, 2011, 123473 (Box 4)
  - Ho, Daniel, 2018-02-10 (Box 4)
  - Ho, Pastor Dan, and Chan, Viola, 2018-02-10 (Box 4)
  - Al Hoang oral history, 2013, 169586 (Box 4)
  - William Hsueh oral history, 168333 (Box 4)
    Includes transcript, consent form, and audio.
  - Hung Hsien oral history, Spring 2017, 2017-05-12 (Box 4)
  - Elsie Lee Huang oral history, Spring 2017 (wrc08596), 2017-07-29 (Box 4)
  - Ingervsen, Antonia, 2018, 2018-10-20 (Box 4)
  - Dr. Sulekh Jain, 2017 (wrc08248) (Box 4)
  - Jain, Urvashi, 2018-07-25 (Box 4)
  - Farzani Jalali, 2013, 172564 (Box 4)
  - Shahid Javed oral history interview, 212187 (Box 4)
    Includes photographs and transcript.
  - Jihuang Ji oral history, 2014-03-29; 181498 (Box 4)
  - Cookie Joe oral history interview, 260396 (Box 4)
    Includes transcript, consent form, and photograph.
  - Glenda Joe, 2017 (wrc08327) (Box 4)
  - Jack Joe oral history, 2014-03-25; 181503 (Box 4)
  - Dr. Daniel Dare Louie oral history, Fall 2017 (wrc08595), 2017-11-05 (Box 4)
  - Yani Rose Keo oral history, 169590 (Box 5)
    Includes transcript, consent form, ephemera related to the Alliance of Multicultural affainrs, and photograph.
  - Khare, Rachna, 2018-06-06 (Box 4)
  - Kiang, Ching-Hwa, 2019-02-08 (Box 5)
  - Lourdes Lee Kong oral history, 2014-04-11; 181508 (Box 5)
  - Kothari, Atul, 2018-02-08 (Box 5)
  - Kumahata, Hajime, 2013; 159607 (Box 5)
    Includes transcript, audio, and photograph.
  - Hajime Jim Kumahata oral history, 168337 (Box 5)
  - Kumar, Rathna, 132901 (Box 5)
    Includes transcript, survey, audio, and photograph.
  - Jimmy Kumana oral history, Summer 2014 (Box 5)
    Includes transcript, consent form, research notes, and photograph.
  - Ty Lam oral history, 2014-04-07; 181513 (Box 5)
  - Le, Huan Ngoc, 159621 (Box 5)
    Includes consent form, transcript, questionnaire, photographs.
  - Le, Nhuan Phu, oral history, 2019-06-28 (Box 5)
  - Le, Thuy Bich, 174340 (Box 5)
  - Chao Chiung Lee oral history, 172550 (Box 5)
  - Lee, Cin-Ty, 2018 (Box 6)
  - Gene L. Lee, 2010, 114912 (Box 5)
  - Lee, Kenneth S., 123471 (Box 5)
  - Lee, Koon Hong Gor (Mrs. Albert Lee) (Box 5)
  - Michelle Lee, 2013, 168341 (Box 5)
    Includes consent form, transcript.
  - Wea Lee, 2010, 114932 (Box 5)
    Includes transcript, consent form, and Southern News Media Group magazines.
  - Lee, Yea Won (not available online), 2020 (Box 5)
  - Li, Jia Ling, 2018-07-09 (Box 5)
  - Tommy Ligh oral history, 172581 (Box 6)
    Includes transcript, consent form, research notes, family tree notes, and photograph.
  - Lin, Chi-Mei Hua, 2018-07-06 (Box 6)
  - Jimmy Lin oral history interview (wrc05767), 212190 (Box 6)
  - Debbie Lin oral history interview (wrc05768), 260397 (Box 6)
  - Melody Mei-Ching Lo oral history, 168345 (Box 6)
  - Lo, Pam, 159611 (Box 6)
  - Lo, Willy, 159615 (Box 6)
    Includes transcript, survey, consent form, and photograph.
  - Mahajan, Devinder, 2018-03-12 (Box 6)
  - Manalo, Matt, 2019-06-12 (Box 6)
  - Sarosh Manekshaw oral history, Summer 2014 (wrc05143) (Box 6)
    ZAH. Includes transcript, consent form, and photograph.
  - Percy Master oral history, Summer 2014 (wrc05144) (Box 6)
  - Christopher Janwong McKiggan oral history, 168349 (Box 6)
  - Noshir Medhora oral history, Summer 2014 (wrc05145) (Box 1)
  - Jehanbux Mehta oral history, Summer 2014 (wrc05146) (Box 6)
  - Mehta, Riya Atul, 2016-03-01 (Box 6)
  - Jehangir Mistry oral history, Summer 2014 (wrc05147) (Box 6)
  - Bobby Joe Moon oral history, 172575 (Box 6)
  - Mamie Moy, 2012, 160613 (Box 6)
    Includes consent form, transcript, questionnaire.
  - Tay Tay Mynt, 2018 (Box 7)
  - Ancheta, Victor Tomas (not available online), 2020-03-05 (Box 1)
  - Divakaruni, Chitra, oral history, 2019-06-24 (Box 3)
  - Gurnani, Roshni (not available online), 2019
  - Agrawal, Sushila oral history, 2019-07-20 (Box 1)
  - Chiao, Leroy, 2019-06-18 (Box 2)
  - Kao, Mandy, 2019-06-20
  - Fish, David, 2019-07-22
- Series II: Oral history interview by last name, N-Z
  - Bob Nguyen, 2012 (Box 7)
  - Nguyen, Anhlan P., 2020-05-23 (Box 7)
    Also includes book "Living in Grace: Living Your Best Life Now" by Anhlan P. Nguyen
  - Danny Nguyen, 2013, 169575 (Box 7)
  - Michael Nguyen oral history, 172636 (Box 7)
  - Nguyen, Van Nam, 2019-06-11
  - Nong, Truong Duy, 2019-03-08 (Box 7)
  - Ong, Natalie, 2017-11-16 (Box 7)
  - Benjamin Ongoco, 160614 (Box 7)
    Includes transcript and photograph.
  - Orchard, William, 132939 (Box 7)
    Includes transcript, research notes, and consent form.No audio is available for this interview.
  - Otto, Rachel Soyon, 159628 (Box 7)
    Includes transcript, survey,photograph, and audio.
  - Dr. Pan Po-Hsi, Fall 2017 (wrc08599) (Box 7)
  - Prospera Laron Panes oral history, 181518 (Box 7)
    Includes transcript, photographs, and consent form.
  - Panis, Rolando, 132937 (Box 7)
  - Violeta Panis oral history, 2014-04-04; 181523 (Box 7)
  - Violeta Panis oral history, 2016 (Box 7)
  - Parameswaran, Lakshmy, 132874 (Box 7)
    Includes transcript,audio, photograph, and survey.
  - Parker, Sonia Fujimoto, 2018-10-23 (Box 7)
  - Shapur Pavri oral history, Summer 2014 (wrc05148) (Box 7)
    ZAH. Includes transcript, photographs, research notes, and consent form.
  - Yasmin Pavri, Summer 2014 (wrc05156) (Box 7)
    Includes transcript, photograph, and consent form.
  - Peralta, Elnora, 132938 (Box 7)
    Includes audio and transcripts.
  - Phan, Cathy, 2017-06-21 (Box 7)
  - Joanna Po oral history (no transcript), 205606 (Box 7)
    Includes photograph and consent form.
  - Poisot, Christina, 132910 (Box 7)
    Includes trancript, audio, survey, photograph, and Holy Rosary Crusade: 25th Anniversary May Crowning, May 28, 2008, Mass program booklet and Souvenir program booklet (Filipino choir featured).
  - Pu, Rose, 2018-06-08 (Box 7)
  - Qian, Mr. Jing, 123468 (Box 8)
  - Yang Qin oral history, 2014-03-22; 181528 (Box 8)
  - Esther Quan, 2010, 114909 (Box 8)
    Includes transcript, consent form and photograph.
  - Gordon Quan oral history, 172600 (Box 8)
    Includes transcript, research notes, consent form, and photograph.
  - Meheryar Noshir Rivetna, Summer 2014 (wrc05150) (Box 8)
    ZAH. Includes transcript, research notes, consent form, survey, corespondence, and photograph.
  - Nathalie Roff, 160615 (Box 8)
    Includes transcript, audio, questionnaire, consent form, and photograph.
  - Royse, Marguerite Gee, 2018-03-05 (Box 8)
  - Aban Rustomji oral history, 172612 (Box 8)
    Includes consent form, transcript, and photographs. Also includes article "Fires" by Debra Kolah.
  - Sagar, Vispi, 2014 (Box 8)
  - Nancy Saibara-Naritomi, 2012, 160616 (Box 8)
    Includes consent form, transcript, photograph, and brief family history document.
  - Samreth, Suphal, 2012, 159640 (Box 8)
    Includes consent form, transcript, and photograph.
  - Sarkar, Ratna G., 2012, 159635 (Box 8)
    Includes consent form, transcript, photograph.
  - Sehba Sarwar, 2013, 172555 (Box 8)
    Includes consent form, transcript, questionnaire, photograph.
  - Nargesh Sethna, 2013, 174646 (Box 8)
    Includes consent form, transcript, interviewee photographs, images of family photographs and documents.
  - Shah, Vibhuti, 2018-06-11 (Box 8)
  - Shehabuddin, Rahnuma (aka Elora Sheabuddin), 2011, 123472 (Box 8)
  - Shen, Guo Liang, 2018-07-09 (Box 8)
  - Shen, Mitsi, 2019-11-21
    Also includes business brochures and newsclippings.
    - Mitsi Shen ballet career digital images, clippings, awards, school photos, 2013 America's Got Talent, and resume, 2010-2020
  - Shih, Hue-Teh, oral history (not available online), 2019-06-17 (Box 8)
  - Shin, Eric, 2012, 159644 (Box 8)
    Includes consent form, transcript, questionnaire, and photograph.
  - Bapsi Sidhwa, 2013, 172588 (Box 8)
    Includes consent form, transcript, questionnaire, interviewee photographs, and images of family photographs.
  - Gregoria Smith, 2014, 205609 (Box 9)
    Includes consent form, transcript, questionnaire, interviewee photographs, and images of family photographs and documents.
  - Kim Soo, 2014, 205610 (Box 9)
    Includes consent form, transcript, questionnaire, interviewee photographs, and images of Kim Soo newsclippings and photographs.
  - Robert M. Su, 2013, 168353 (Box 9)
    Includes consent form, transcript, and questionnaire.
  - Sun, Y. Ping, 2011, 132873 (Box 9)
    Includes consent form, transcript, questionnaire and photograph.
  - Sung, Thomas, 2018-10-11 (Box 9)
    Also includes book "Liu-Li Fei and Opera"
  - Verma Maria Tadeo, 2014, 205611 (Box 9)
    Includes consent form, transcript, questionnaire, and photographs.
  - Takehara, Kenneth, 2011, 132920 (Box 9)
    Includes consent form and transcript for 2011 interview. Also donated at the time of that interview were other interview recordings and materials as listed here: Takehara family scrapbook (print from PDF copy); State of Texas certificate commissioning 442nd Regimental Combat Team, World War II, as Honorary Texas Citizens, signed by Texas Gov. John Connally, Oct. 21, 1963; Program for Congressional Gold Medal Ceremony, Houston, TX, Feb. 19, 2012; program for National Japanese American Memorial Foundation Awards Dinner Gala 2009; "Go for Broke" Takehara interview on DVD, undated, untranscribed; WWII 42nd interview on DVD, 2003, untranscribed. Rights to share these interviews publicly online were not expressly included with the donation.
  - Takehara, Marion (Mrs. Kenneth Takehara), 2011, 132921 (Box 9)
  - Julie Yau Yee Tam, 2013, 168357 (Box 9)
    Includes consent form, transcript, questionnaire, student interviewer summary, photograph.
  - Thompson, Edna, 2011, 123474 (Box 9)
  - Thuy, Vu Thanh, 2018-07-02 (Box 9)
  - Tipton, Mary, 159649 (Box 9)
    Includes consent form, transcript, and images of family photographs and objects, annotated on the print out.
  - Tran, Mai, 123466 (Box 10)
  - Tran, Michelle, 159652 (Box 10)